Guide to the Signal Corps, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Signal Corps, Yale University, records
1917-1919
RU 90
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The records consist of correspondence, reports, course descriptions, financial records, and personnel files documenting the Signal Corps School for Officer Candidates at Yale.
Yale University. Signal Corps
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 42-A (YRG 42-A), Records of military training programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically by subject.
Biographical / Historical
The Signal Corps School for Officer Candidates was established at Yale in 1918.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, course descriptions, financial records, and personnel files documenting the Signal Corps School for Officer Candidates at Yale.
Military training camps -- United States; World War, 1914-1918 -- Education and the war; World War, 1914-1918 -- War work -- Schools; World War, 1914-1918 -- United States; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Signal Corps
- Administrative files and personal records, circa 1917-1919; Accession 19ND-A-176
  - Bills, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
  - Correspondence
    - 1918 Sep (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1918 Oct 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1918 Oct 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1918 Nov 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1918 Nov 16-30 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1918 Dec (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1919 Jan (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Course Descriptions, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 11 - 12)
  - Information and Procedures, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Files
    - Assignment Rosters, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Discharge Lists, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Enlistment and Transfer Forms (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Individual Records (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Officer Candidates, 1918 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 18 - 20)
    - Supply Service applications (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Radio Log, North Sheffield Station, 1918 October 21-November 26 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Reimbursement Correspondence, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Steno Pad, 1918 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Weekly and Monthly Reports, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
  - Index of photographs. For photos see YRG 48-A Yale Picture Collection, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 27)